they've got louder every time I don't
每次我不大声大声
think the clacker will make it through
认为敲手会成功
take five Oh canvas with with with the
带五张哦帆布一起用
pixels or if then pixels of course comes
像素，或者如果像素当然会出现
with being around a while yeah it's been
大约有一段时间了
I think it's actually pretty underused
我认为它实际上没有被充分利用
because sometimes really have like
因为有时候真的有喜欢
affect people like bend over backwards
影响人们喜欢向后弯腰
to implement it with dom elements so i
用dom元素实现它，所以我
do that
去做
it's just simple because then i can use
这很简单，因为那时我可以使用
it's not the transition like if I think
这不是我想的那种过渡
I'm a zest like some spinners if I look
我看起来像一些微调的人一样热情
at the spinner that you put in Skoosh
在您放入Skoosh的微调器中
I'd yeah but I got snippets that copy
是的，但是我得到了复制的摘要
canvas yeah okay that would and you'll
帆布，是的，那你会
be interesting to compare the
比较有趣
performance actually for this yeah
实际表现是这样的
and on the spinners I did on the HTTP to
在微调器上，我在HTTP上执行了
a free app thing there a radio progress
一个免费的应用程序，那里有一个广播进度
bar thing is yes there
酒吧的事是有的
darah SVG they're not canvas so we're
darah SVG他们不是帆布，所以我们
talking about them what I was just
谈论他们我只是
saying it's easier to do it in SVG I
说在SVG中做起来更容易
understand why people don't use canvas
了解为什么人们不使用画布
okay and that's the end of this to be
好的，这就是结束
fair like round things in canvas I find
很像我发现的画布上的圆形东西
possum because you only have RS and
负鼠，因为你只有RS和
several where's the circle command arcs
圆的命令弧在哪里
parameters are so unintuitive it's yes
参数太不直观了，是的
yes it's irritating but what I wanna
是的，这很烦人，但我想
talk about is the newer kind of stuff
谈论的是新事物
that's arriving hey so and the stuff new
到了，嘿，新的东西
your kind of stuff so what's in chrome
你的东西，所以铬
now and I think of a browser as well I
现在，我也想到了浏览器
think it's it's definitely in Firefox
认为肯定是在Firefox中
its off-screen canvas yes Oscars premise
它的屏幕外画布是奥斯卡的前提
I mean that's it's the same canvas it's
我的意思是那是同一张画布
the same same same API you get the same
相同的相同的API，您得到的相同
dry bits yep but actually out you go but
是的，但是实际上你出去了
what is new about it Jake I don't know
有什么新消息，杰克，我不知道
tell me please poop it's the same canvas
告诉我，请便便是同一张画布
it's got the same draw bits but it's
它有相同的吸引点，但是
off-screen no it's it's in a worker and
屏幕外否，是因为它在工作人员中，
that's it yeah that's but became
是的，但后来变成了
constructed in a worker and user to
在工人和用户中建造
generate graphics and then send them
生成图形然后发送
over the myth FET right you send them
通过神话FET，你发送给他们
over to the main thread and so it's that
转到主线程，就是这样
you can do all your complicated work in
您可以在其中完成所有复杂的工作
a worker and then just send no transfer
一个工人，然后不发送任何调动
because it's also do a WebGL so this is
因为它也可以做WebGL，所以这是
this is the thing about the browser
这是关于浏览器的事情
support is we support 2d and WebGL
支持就是我们支持2d和WebGL
I believe Firefox on you supports WebGL
我相信您的Firefox支持WebGL
only WebGL yeah interesting it's part of
只有WebGL是的，有趣的是
their you know thing to do games yeah
他们知道做游戏的事吗
focus so it's WebGL I'm interested in it
专注于WebGL我对此很感兴趣
from doing things like image decoding
做像图像解码之类的事情
off the main thread which you should be
离开主线程，你应该
able to just know I was interested and I
能够知道我有兴趣，而我
have no idea I have no idea at all I
我完全不知道
mean to Faraday's image decoding
意味着法拉第的图像解码
actually there is image decode now which
实际上现在有图像解码
decodes an image off thread yes just go
线程外解码图像，可以
doesn't give you the pixels no sure but
不确定不会给您像素
I'm saying like you know forward but
我是说你知道前进，但是
here say I think Paul Lewis a long while
在这里说我想保罗·刘易斯很久了
ago wrote a blog post where he actually
之前写了一篇博客文章，他实际上
decoded images in a worker with canvas
用画布在工人中解码的图像
to basically not block the main thread
基本上不阻塞主线程
with a decoding which used to be a thing
过去曾经是解码的东西
that decoding is locked the main thread
解码锁定主线程
now browsers just decode in a different
现在浏览器只是以不同的方式解码
thread under the hood yeah ii you want
你想要的引擎盖下的线程
to get to the pixels or do some
达到像素或做一些
manipulation or maybe scale it and to
操纵或扩展它并
store less on disk or something yeah
少存储在磁盘或其他东西上
that becomes really handy you're doing
这真的很方便
all the cameras work that's main thread
所有相机都是主线
based so yeah yeah do it all and work
根据，是的，是的，所有的工作
and then just send the done image so do
然后只发送完成的图像
you have to like create an off-screen
你必须喜欢创建一个屏幕外
canvas and then write piping to bring it
画布，然后编写管道将其携带
on screen once it's done it's very much
在屏幕上完成后，非常
data or you can transfer the canvas from
数据，也可以从
the main thread to the worker and then
主线程到工人，然后
just sort of operate on it in the worker
只是在工人身上进行操作
oh that's just magically yeah that's a
哦，那真是不可思议，是的，
little so it could be good for that will
一点点，所以这可能会好
be good for games where you have like
适用于喜欢的游戏
the game logic probably running into
游戏逻辑可能会遇到
work and you say like you draw on a
工作，你说就像你画一个
canvas and it gets inked to the main
帆布，它被涂在主体上
thread you get requestanimationframe now
线程，您现在获得requestanimationframe
in a worker that's interested one of the
在一个感兴趣的工人中
things that you would need for that true
真正需要的东西
yeah you wouldn't need that which is
是的，您不需要的是
pretty cool
很酷
I'm not sure how that works if you've
我不确定如果您已经
got two monitors of different
有两个不同的显示器
refresh rates it maybe figure it out
刷新率也许可以弄清楚
because it knows where the cameras I
因为它知道我的相机在哪里
mean yeah Chrome already figures out the
是的，Chrome已经知道
resolution as well like you literally
分辨率和字面上一样
can move from high DPI to low dpi here
可以从高DPI移至低dpi
it just works
它只是工作
exactly but the problem is it's a tab
确切的是，但问题是它是一个选项卡
that knows that whereas if you're in a
那知道，而如果你在一个
worker you're not in the tab so what its
工作人员，您不在选项卡中，那么它
associated with it is strongly
与之紧密相关
associated with the renderer so it
与渲染器相关联，因此
should it should work yes so that's the
它应该工作是吗，所以
thing and I I think I'll be useful you I
我认为我会有用的
think it's exact puzzle piece honestly
说实话这是完全正确的拼图
well and there's other cases it unlocks
好，还有其他情况可以解锁
not just a performance case of you
不只是您的表演案例
things like if you get a push
像是你被推
notification in a serviceworker and you
服务人员中的通知，您
have like avatars cached
像头像一样被缓存
yeah but you're it's a group message you
是的，但是你是群​​发消息
could construct an icon true but what
可以构造一个图标为true，但是
made up of or like badging like there's
由或像徽章那样组成
five new messages now so you're gonna
现在有五个新消息，所以您要
change the exactly yeah and you could do
完全改变是的，你可以做
that and without having to go to the so
而且不必去做
that's actually super useful not that so
这实际上是超级有用的，不是这样
yeah so that's one bit and we've gotten
是的，这只是一点，我们已经
our clickers you can also do like video
我们的点击器，您也可以喜欢视频
transcoding potentially in a worker
可能在工作人员中进行代码转换
maybe on I mean know if you had a bowl
也许我的意思是知道你是否有碗
the streaming stuff and maybe I mean
流媒体的东西，也许我的意思是
canvas technically is able to play
从技术上讲，画布能够播放
videos in a way right you can take a
影片，您可以采取
video element and just decode everywhere
视频元素，随处解码
so we don't have a video I'm and welcome
所以我们没有视频欢迎我
and that's the missing piece so
那是缺少的部分
immediate a lot of the media api's are
立即许多媒体API是
missing from workers right now it's
现在工人不见了
something they're looking at gang and I
他们在看帮派和我的东西
think especially as you know we'll start
尤其是想想，我们将开始
to do more media stuff that isn't real
做更多不真实的媒体工作
time based yeah I think that's when it
基于时间，是的，我认为是在那时
makes sense start having that in a
有道理开始
worker yeah that's really cool because I
工人，是的，这真的很酷，因为我
write right now a lot of the media
现在写很多媒体
streams are based around to the WebRTC
流基于WebRTC
so like it's all based on you know
所以这一切都是基于你知道的
dropping frames if it's not real time
如果不是实时的，丢帧
that's yeah like video processing yeah
是的，就像视频处理一样
you're gonna animal we have it with
你会成为动物，我们拥有
audio worklet where you can like do an
您可以在其中进行音频工作的地方
audio web audio api know the audio for
音频Web音频api知道音频
it specifically but Web Audio API we can
具体来说，但我们可以使用Web Audio API
do an offline context to just generate
做一个离线的背景，只是产生
audio would be cool to have the same
音频会很棒
thing for video because exactly if you
视频的东西，因为如果你
could like generate videos like do a
想产生像
like mini video editor would be so cool
像迷你视频编辑器一样酷
to build on the web and say this vision
在网络上建立并说出这一愿景
coders and the browser already for web
编码器和已经用于Web的浏览器
app you see why can't we access them
应用程序，您会看到我们为什么无法访问它们
forever so that's cool another canvas
永远，所以这很酷
thing well that's another one yeah this
很好，那是另外一个
one is super experimental only in Chrome
一个仅在Chrome中具有超级实验性
behind flag sort of stuff that's sort of
标记后面的东西
experimental okay is there looking at
实验还可以吗
low latency canvas ah and this is an
低延迟画布啊，这是一个
option you would pass into the canvas
您将传递到画布的选项
when you're I think it's when you're
当你是我的时候
getting the context in the 2d context
在2d上下文中获取上下文
and like what makes it low latency it
像是什么使它具有低延迟
okay so in terms of web standards mm-hmm
好的，就网络标准而言，mm-hmm
what it does is it it sits outside the
它所做的是它位于外部
event loop so right now we can only
事件循环，所以现在我们只能
paint at that particular point yeah an
在那个特定点画画是的
event loop and if something else is
事件循环，如果还有其他事情
blocking you actually batch up the the
实际阻止了您
draw instructions and then I guess we
绘制说明，然后我猜我们
partly they're UNIX you know that you PU
他们是UNIX的一部分，您知道您PU
but whatever like we just execute a
但是无论我们执行什么
batch of draw calls and then yes and so
一批抽签，然后是，等等
it means that if you like something has
这意味着，如果你喜欢的东西有
changed on the page like the the Dom
像Dom一样在页面上更改
painting is gonna be synchronous with
绘画将与
the canvas painting which is what you
帆布画就是你
want in a lot of cases yeah but
在很多情况下都想要
it also can delay things going onto the
这也可能会延迟事物进入
canvas and yes it's batching up all of
画布，是的，它正在堆积所有
these calls sometimes it's batching up
这些电话有时正在堆积
the whole image great yeah double
整个图像很棒，是的
buffering right is that you know these
缓冲权是你知道这些
times better than I do
比我好
it's that's pretty much a gaming
那几乎是一场游戏
practice because when the GPU renders
练习是因为当GPU渲染时
like it first a draws you know the
首先喜欢它，您会知道
background then the couple of polygons
然后是几个多边形
at the back and so if you don't do
在后面，所以如果你不这样做
bubble buffering
气泡缓冲
buh-buh-buh-buh-buh buffering double
buh-buh-buh-buh-buh缓冲双
buffering and your GPU is forced to ship
缓冲，您的GPU被迫运送
a frame because frame rate you might
一帧，因为您可能会使用帧速率
have an incomplete picture and then you
画面不完整，然后你
get like this weird thing where you have
变得像这样奇怪的事情
tearing or you have like yep things
泪流满面或你喜欢
building up over a frame even you don't
即使没有，也可以在框架上堆积
want that so that's you have a buffer
想要那个，那就是你有一个缓冲区
where they're ready both images in you
他们准备好了您的两张图片
build up the next frame in a separate
单独建立下一个框架
buffer and you swap them so this is the
缓冲区，您交换它们，所以这是
first one along with the tearing so if
第一个连同撕裂，所以如果
you end up with just one set of bytes
最终只有一组字节
representing the image content of that
代表那个的图像内容
canvas so if you're you know if you
帆布所以如果你知道你是否
weren't using requestanimationframe
没有使用requestanimationframe
properly or you got half of your finger
正确地或您的手指伸了一半
on mmm you will end up with half for the
在mmm上，您将得到一半
thing on the page there so well I mean
页面上的东西很好，我的意思是
that first it sounds like that's the
首先听起来像是
step backwards but in the other on the
向后退，但在另一侧
other hand it puts you in control
另一方面让您掌控一切
doesn't it yeah it's so it's useful for
是不是，所以它对
things like a drawing app where you're
诸如绘图应用程序之类的地方
taking stylus input and drawing a
接受手写笔输入并绘制一个
straight away there's no tearing issue
马上就没有撕裂的问题
there yeah and you really want a slow
是的，你真的想要一个慢
latency as opposed to make it feel as
延迟而不是让它感觉像
natural as you possibly can right
你可能会自然而然的
exactly and it's also like in in the
完全一样，也就像在
Dana Jeff where wasm is a thing if you
达娜·杰夫（Dana Jeff）
compile an existing C++ drawing live it
实时编译现有的C ++绘图
already has double buffering in there
那里已经有双重缓冲
exactly so you end up with double
正是这样，您最终会获得两倍
buffering
缓冲
o ends and so this is a way of opting
o结束，所以这是一种选择
out of that and then you just keep the
从那，然后你只要保持
buffering that your game engine has to
缓冲您的游戏引擎必须
look for so yeah and that is pretty much
寻找，是的，这差不多
all I know about it right now
我现在所知道的一切
pastor looks at demo and we'll post the
牧师看演示，我们将发布
links to it and I was never on an
链接到它，我从来没有
article about the Austrian cameras which
关于奥地利相机的文章
was later yep and we'll link to the demo
后来是的，我们将链接到演示
of the canvas the low latency canvas
画布的低延迟画布
look that I don't know it alone no no
看起来我并不孤单
it's just excite about it isn't he yeah
只是很兴奋，不是吗
it's just excited about it was done by
我很高兴这是由
the engineer who did the implementation
实施的工程师
do you know if I think okay
你知道我是否认为还可以
I don't know their full name but it's it
我不知道他们的全名，但仅此而已
works it crushed Chrome a couple of
可以将Chrome压碎
times for me so that's how experimental
对我来说是次
we're talking but it's really exciting
我们在说话，但真的很令人兴奋
and it I because it's just simple
我，因为它很简单
drawing app I would love a side-by-side
绘图应用程序，我很喜欢并排
example because I can't decide if it's
例子，因为我无法确定是否
like placebo effects that it feels
就像安慰剂一样
faster because you know I'm told this is
更快，因为您知道我被告知这是
low latency cameras like whoa look how
低延迟摄像头，如哇，看起来如何
low latency is that that line really
低延迟是那条线真的
appeared on screen fast as I've ever
像我以前一样快速出现在屏幕上
seen it appear for so I you know I it's
看到它出现了所以我你知道我是
very obviously very important for game
对游戏非常重要
engines and that kind of I would like to
引擎，我想
see some science behind how much faster
看一些科学背后有多快
it is on like a phone especially yeah
就像电话一样，特别是
but yeah that's sometimes it takes up a
但是是的，有时它会占用一个
mic one armpit just goes that was that
麦克风一个腋下就这样
was me before I oh not last year the
是我之前，我不是去年
year before yeah because I picked a
是的，因为我选了一个
t-shirt I want it to wear as an f1
我想要它作为F1穿着的T恤
t-shirt was like yeah when my on t-shirt
T恤就像是的，当我穿上T恤时
and then just before going on stage
然后就在上台前
pretty much I just looked round this up
我几乎只是四处寻找
just yet this armpit this one dry as a
只是这个腋下干了一个
bone this one
骨头这一个